<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  - SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
  - SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2020-2021 Carl Schwan <carlschwan@kde.org>
 -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.kregexpeditor</id>
  <provides>
    <binary>kregexpeditor</binary>
  </provides>
  <name>KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">محرر التعابير النمطية</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KRegExpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KRegexpEditor</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">K Düzenli İfade Düzenleyicisi</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KRegExpEditor</name>
  <summary>Edit regular expression</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">حرر تعبير نمطي</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Edició d'expressió regular</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Editeu expressió regular</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Editar expresión regular</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Modifier l'expression régulière</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">עריכת ביטויים רגולריים</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Modifica le espressioni regolari</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">რეგულარული გამოსახულების ჩასწორება</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Reguliere expressie bewerken</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytuj wyrażenie regularne</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Editor de expressão regular</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Urejanje regularnega izraza</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Düzenli ifadeleri düzenleyin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редагування формального виразу</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KRegexpEditor is a lightweight KDE application designed to help you create, test, and refine regular expressions with ease. It provides an interactive visual interface that highlights matches in real time, supports common regex syntax features, and offers helpful tools to build complex patterns without memorizing every rule.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">محرر التعابير النمطية هو تطبيق كيدي خفيف الوزن مصمم لمساعدتك على إنشاء واختبار وتحسين التعبيرات النمطية بسهولة. يوفر واجهة مرئية تفاعلية تُبرز التطابقات آنيًا، ويدعم ميزات بناء الجملة الشائعة للتعبيرات النمطية، ويوفر أدوات مفيدة لبناء أنماط معقدة دون الحاجة إلى حفظ كل قاعدة.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KRegexpEditor és una aplicació lleugera de KDE dissenyada per a ajudar-vos a crear, provar i refinar expressions regulars amb facilitat. Proporciona una interfície visual interactiva que ressalta les coincidències en temps real, admet funcions comunes de sintaxi d'expressió regular, i ofereix eines útils per construir patrons complexos sense memoritzar cada regla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KRegexpEditor és una aplicació lleugera de KDE dissenyada per ajudar-vos a crear, provar i refinar expressions regulars amb facilitat. Proporciona una interfície visual interactiva que ressalta les coincidències en temps real, admet característiques comunes de sintaxi d'expressió regular, i oferix eines útils per a construir patrons complexos sense memoritzar cada regla.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KRegexpEditor es una aplicación ligera de KDE diseñada para ayudarle a crear, probar y refinar expresiones regulares con facilidad. Proporciona una interfaz visual interactiva que resalta las coincidencias en tiempo real, permite funciones de sintaxis comunes de expresiones regulares y ofrece útiles herramientas para crear patrones complejos sin necesidad de memorizar todas las reglas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KRegexpEditor est une application pour KDE, légère et conçue pour vous aider à créer, tester et affiner facilement des expressions régulières. Il fournit une interface visuelle interactive mettant en évidence les correspondances en temps réel. Elle prend en charge les fonctionnalités de syntaxe « regex » classique et offre des outils utiles pour créer des structures complexes sans mémoriser chaque règle.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KRegexpEditor הוא יישום KDE קליל שתוכנן לסייע לך ליצור, לבדוק ולטייב ביטויים רגולריים בקלות. הוא מספק ממשק חזותי אינראקטיבי שמדגיש התאמות בזמן אמת, תומך ביכולות נפוצות של תחביר ביטוי רגולרי ומציע כלים חיוניים לבניית תבניות מורכבות מבלי לזכור את כל אחד מהכללים בעל פה.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KRegexpEditor è un'applicazione KDE leggera progettata per aiutarti a creare, testare e perfezionare le espressioni regolari con facilità. Offre un'interfaccia visiva interattiva che evidenzia le corrispondenze in tempo reale, supporta le funzionalità di sintassi delle espressioni regolari più comuni e offre strumenti utili per creare schemi complessi senza dover memorizzare ogni regola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KRegExpEditor მსუბუქი აპლიკაციაა KDE-ისთვის, რომელიც შექმნილია, რომ დაგეხმაროთ, იოლად შექმნათ, შეამოწმოთ და დახვეწოთ რეგულარული გამოსახულებები. ის მოგაწვდით ინტერაქტიულ ვიზუალურ ინტერფეისს, რომელიც გამოკვეთს დამთხვევებს რეალურ დროში, აქვს ზოგადი რეგგამოსის სინტაქსის ფუნქციებიდა გთავაზობთ სასარგებლო ხელსაწყოებს, ააგოთ რთული ნიმუშები თითოეული წესის დამახსოვრების გარეშე.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KRegexpEditor is een lichtgewicht KDE toepassing ontworpen om u te helpen bij het gemakkelijk aanmaken, testen en verfijnen van reguliere expressies. Het biedt een interactief visueel interface dat overeenkomsten in realtime accentueert, algemene regex syntaxis-functies accentueert en behulpzame hulpmiddelen biedt om complexe patronen te bouwen zonder elke regel te onthouden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KRegexpEditor jest lekką aplikacją KDE stworzoną do pomagania w pisaniu, testowaniu, dopracowywaniu wyrażeń regularnych. Dostarcza interaktywnego interfejsu wizualnego, który podświetla pasujące wyrażenia w czasie rzeczywistym, obsługuje złożoną składnię wyrażeń regularnych oraz zawiera inne pomocne narzędzia do budowania złożonych wyrażeń bez konieczności pamiętania o każdej z zasad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KRegexpEditor é um aplicativo leve do KDE, projetado para ajudar você a criar, testar e refinar expressões regulares com facilidade. Ele oferece uma interface visual interativa que destaca correspondências em tempo real, suporta recursos comuns de sintaxe regex e oferece ferramentas úteis para criar padrões complexos sem precisar memorizar todas as regras.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KRegexpEditor je lahka aplikacija za KDE, zasnovana za enostavno ustvarjanje, testiranje in izpopolnjevanje regularnih izrazov. Ponuja interaktivni vizualni vmesnik, ki sproti označuje ujemanja, podpira običajne funkcije sintakse regularnih izrazov in ponuja uporabna orodja za gradnjo kompleksnih vzorcev, ne da bi si morali zapomniti vsako pravilo.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">K Düzenli İfade Düzenleyicisi, düzenli ifadeleri kolayca oluşturmanıza, sınamanıza ve geliştirmenize yardımcı olmak için tasarlanmış hafif bir KDE uygulamasıdır. Eşleşmeleri gerçek zamanlı olarak vurgulayan etkileşimli bir görsel arayüz sunar, yaygın düzenli ifade sözdizimi özelliklerini destekler ve her kuralı ezberlemeden karmaşık kalıplar oluşturmanıza yardımcı araçlar sunar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KRegexpEditor є невибагливою до ресурсів програмою KDE, яку розроблено для допомоги у створенні, перевірці та удосконаленні формальних виразів. У ній реалізовано інтерактивний візуальний інтерфейс, який інтерактивно підсвічує відповідники, підтримує загальні можливості синтаксису формальних виразів і пропонує корисні інструменти для побудови складних взірців без потреби у запам'ятовуванні кожного з правил.</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/kregexpeditor/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?product=kregexpeditor</url>
  <categories>
    <category>Utilities</category>
  </categories>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0</project_license>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#cdecfc</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#17a3ea</color>
  </branding>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.kregexpeditor.desktop</launchable>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
